<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Visualization &#43; Analytics on Caitlyn</title>
    <link>/datavisualization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Visualization &#43; Analytics on Caitlyn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/datavisualization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Office Dialogue in Five Charts</title>
      <link>/datavisualization/theoffice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/datavisualization/theoffice/</guid>
      <description>Summer 2017 The Pudding, in conjunction with Russel Goldberg
Pinpointed an interesting topic in pop culture, created a dataset through web scraping in Python, worked with the database in SQL, drew interesting conclusions, programmed a Markov Chain text simulator, conducted sentiment analysis on large swaths of text data, mocked up design ideas, and worked with Russell Goldberg of The Pudding to make the graphics come to life.
See it here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How far is too far?</title>
      <link>/datavisualization/clinics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/datavisualization/clinics/</guid>
      <description>An analysis of driving times to abortion clinics in the US. Summer 2017 The Pudding, in conjunction with Russel Goldberg and Amber Thomas
Catalyzed work on this impactful essay, conducted weeks of background research to grasp such a complex and controversial topic, reached out and interviewed experts in the field, manually created complete datasets of abortion clinics locations and procedures in 12 states, and teamed up Russell Goldberg and Amber Thomas of The Pudding to complete the dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How have Warped Tour’s genres evolved over time?</title>
      <link>/datavisualization/warpedtour/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/datavisualization/warpedtour/</guid>
      <description>Summer 2017 The Pudding
Pinpointed another interesting topic in pop culture, created a dataset through web scraping in Python, worked with the database in SQL, drew interesting conclusions, mocked up design ideas, coded a visualization in D3 with design assistance from Matt Daniels of The Pudding.
See it here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Approach to Analyzing RS-fMRI Data</title>
      <link>/datavisualization/fmri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/datavisualization/fmri/</guid>
      <description>Summer 2016 The Mind Research Network, Albuquerque, New Mexico
 Coded a new algorithm for a more descriptive temporal analysis of fMRI images in the resting-state. The goal was to write a method that provided researchers more information than traditional analysis methods, such as Independent Component Analysis, currently tell us about neuroimages. Also programmed a way to visualize the results of this analysis algorithm as clearly and descriptively as possible. Presented findings to staff at the Mind Research Network and the Lovelace Respiratory Research Institute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-Based White Matter Imaging in VCI</title>
      <link>/datavisualization/vci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/datavisualization/vci/</guid>
      <description>Summer 2015 The Mind Research Network, Albuquerque, New Mexico
 Conducted various exploratory analyses to research if diffusion based white matter imaging could be a biomarker for the neurodegenerative disease Vascular Cognitive Impairment (the second leading cause of dementia behind Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s). The goal was to analyze diffusion tensor imaging&amp;rsquo;s (DTI) fractional anisotropy (FA), axial diffusivity (AD), and radial diffusivity (RD) to find the most descriptive diffusion property in classifying subjects and the most affected brain regions in VCI patients.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>